Anders G. Nordby



Motzfeldtsgate 14, N-0187 Oslo, NORWAY (+47) 932 20 333 anders@delichon.no http://delichon.no/services/anders/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/agnordby/

DESCRIPTION

Anders is a project manager, systems architect and senior developer with customer focus and many years of experience in the industry. He holds the **PRINCE2 Practitioner**, **PRINCE2 Foundation** and **Certified Scrum Master** certifications, and he has also had the role of *team leader* and *scrum master* in several projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

05.2019 - PRESENT

Delichon AS

Systems Architect & Senior Developer

Roles: Daily Manager and currently the only employee.

Customers: ABB, Frank Resource Group.

Technologies: Azure DevOps, Akka.NET, TypeScript, React JS, C#, Microsoft .NET Core 2.2, ASP.NET Core MVC, Keycloak, TFS, Git.

01.2018 - 04.2019

Sopra Steria

Lead Software Engineer

Roles: In-house architect responsible for planning and QA of offers to customers. Senior developer for some customers.

Customers: Skatteetaten, Helsedirektoratet.

Technologies: C#, .Net, Episerver CMS, ASP.NET MVC, Microsoft SQL Server, JavaScript, Jira, Confluence, TFS, Git.

03.2014 - 08.2017

CGI

Senior Web Developer

Roles: Team-leder, scrum master, hands-on architect.

Customers: ASKO, Fellesforbundet, Tekna, PIA, Miljødirektoratet. **Technologies:** C#, .Net, inRiver PIM, Apptus eSales, Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, IdentityServer, T-SQL, WebAPI, NServiceBus, Jira, Confluence, jMeter, BlazeMeter, Angular.js, Knockout.js.

03.2014 - 08.2017

Making Waves / Tarantell Senior Systems Consultant

Roles: Senior developer and team leader in several customer projects. Customers: The Norwegian Government, Arcus, The Norwegian Board of Health Administration, Canal Digital Kabel, Synoptik, NMD. Technologies: C#, .Net, NewRelic, PowerShell, jQuery, PowerShell, Jira, Confluence, TFS, SubVersion

| 08.2008 – 12.2009 | Creuna, Consultant / Systems Developer |
|-------------------|--|
| 02.2006 - 07.2008 | Ocelluz, Systems Developer & Project Manager |
| 10.2004 - 02.2008 | Anders Nordby Konsulenttjenester |
| 05.1995 – 06.2002 | Ajilon, Consultant |
| 08.1994 - 07.1995 | Gran skole, Substitute Teacher |

KEY COMPETENCIES

Processes

Systemarkitektur, Scrum, Kanban, prosjektledelse.

Development

Episerver CMS, Episerver Commerce, Episerver Find, C#, ASP.Net, MVC, Apptus eSales, inRiver PIM, IdentityServer, T-SQL, PL/SQL, JavaScript, JSON, Ajax, NServiceBus, WCF, WebServices, REST, WebAPI, XML, HTML, CSS, jQuery, PowerShell, LATEX.

Tools

Jira, Confluence, Git, TFS, SubVersion, ReSharper, NewRelic, jMeter, BlazeMeter, NuGet.

CERTIFICATIONS

| 2020 | Microsoft Azure Fundamentals |
|------|-------------------------------|
| 2019 | PRINCE2 Practitioner |
| 2019 | Certified Scrum Master |
| 2019 | Certified Episerver Developer |
| 2018 | PRINCE2 Foundation |
| 2016 | Certified inRiver Developer |
| | |

COURSES

| 2019 | Tom Gilb: Architecture Workshop |
|------|--|
| 2018 | Sopra Steria: Arkitekturskolen |
| 2015 | Microsoft: Lead Enterprise Architect Programme |

EDUCATION

| 2003 – 2004 | University of Oslo, Teacher Training | | | |
|-------------|--------------------------------------|--|--|--|
| 1999 – 2000 | Oslo Business Academy, IT Candidate | | | |
| 1987 – 1996 | University of Oslo, Cand.Mag. | | | |
| 1984 – 1987 | Eikeli High School, Natural Sciences | | | |

AWARDS

2013-2017 Episerver Most Valued Professional

LANGUAGES

| EXCELLENT | Norwegian (native), English |
|--------------|-----------------------------|
| INTERMEDIATE | Bulgarian |
| BEGINNER | Spanish, German, Japanese |